<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-10-28T15:58:41-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Amanda’s Notes</title><subtitle>Hello!</subtitle><author><name>Amanda</name></author><entry><title type="html">Hello</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/10/28/hello.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hello" /><published>2018-10-28T13:52:03-07:00</published><updated>2018-10-28T13:52:03-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/10/28/hello</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/10/28/hello.html">&lt;p&gt;It’s been roughly 3 months since moving to Seattle and starting a new job. I came here knowing hardly anyone,
and knowing even fewer people who didn’t work at Amazon.
Seeking out places to relax and unwind and find happy food came to be one of my favorite activities, and I wanted to
start a journal of the places that I go to, partially because I want to prove to myself that I don’t spend &lt;strong&gt;all&lt;/strong&gt; my
weekdays and weekends staring at a computer screen, and partially because I came here not knowing where to start picking
up on the snacking so here we are…&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Amanda</name></author><summary type="html">It’s been roughly 3 months since moving to Seattle and starting a new job. I came here knowing hardly anyone, and knowing even fewer people who didn’t work at Amazon. Seeking out places to relax and unwind and find happy food came to be one of my favorite activities, and I wanted to start a journal of the places that I go to, partially because I want to prove to myself that I don’t spend all my weekdays and weekends staring at a computer screen, and partially because I came here not knowing where to start picking up on the snacking so here we are…</summary></entry></feed>